Guide to the Yale Summer and Special Programs Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Administrative records, 1980-1995; Accession 2003-A-060
  - 1984-1985
    - 1985 Course of Study Committee (Box 1)
    - 1985 Dance (Box 1)
    - 1985 ELOP (Box 1)
    - 1985 Faculty Salaries (Box 1)
    - YSP Health Plan (Box 1)
    - 1982-85 Yale-Hopkins Seminar Teaching Soviet History (Box 1)
    - 1985 Humanities and Social Science (Box 1)
    - Info Booklet (Box 1)
    - Lectures (Box 1)
    - YSP Questions (Box 1)
    - Library (Box 1)
    - 1980-85 YSP NEH Seminars (Box 1)
    - NER Comp (Box 1)
    - 1985 Residential College (Box 1)
    - 1985 Scholarships (Box 1)
    - 1985 Science and Mathematics (Box 1)
    - 1985 SLI (Box 1)
    - 1985 Tuition (Box 1)
    - Visiting Faculty 1980-84 (Box 1)
    - Humanities and Social Sciences (Box 1)
    - NAASS-New Haven 1984 (Box 1)
    - YSP - prop (Box 1)
    - 1984 Review Committee (Box 1)
    - 1984 Scholarships (Box 1)
    - 1984 Sciences (Box 1)
    - Tuition Summer Programs (Box 1)
    - WBandC (Box 1)
    - 1984 SLI (Box 1)
    - Special Students, 1980-1984 (Box 1)
    - Review Committee Report, 1984 (Box 1)
  - 1986-1988
    - 1986 Korea seminars NEH (Box 2)
    - 1986 Language Lab (Box 2)
    - 1986 Lectures, concerts (Box 2)
    - 1986 Scholarships (Box 2)
    - 1986 Science and Math (Box 2)
    - 1986 Slavic Languages Proposal (Box 2)
    - 1986 SLI (Box 2)
    - 1986 Adult Programs (Box 2)
    - 1986 Annual Report (Box 2)
    - 1986 Counselor Reports (Box 2)
    - 1986 Brochure (Box 2)
    - 1986 Budget (Box 2)
    - 1986 Conferences (Box 2)
    - 1986 ELOP (Box 2)
    - 1986 Faculty Salaries (Box 2)
    - 1986 Hamlin Interdisciplinary Studies in the Humanities Proposal (Box 2)
    - Participants Adult Programs 1986 Week 6/22-6/27 (Box 2)
    - Museum Programs 1986 (Box 2)
    - Lectures 1986 (Box 2)
    - Museum Programs for Adults (Box 2)
    - Art Gallery Adult Programs (Box 2)
    - Peabody Museum Adult Programs 1986 (Box 2)
    - Originals Adult Programs 1986 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence Adult Programs 1986 (Box 2)
    - Housing Adult Programs 1986 (Box 2)
    - Packets Adult Programs 1986 (Box 2)
    - Adult Program Enrollments (Box 2)
    - Participants Adult Programs 1986 Week 6/15-5/20 (Box 2)
    - Personnel 1986 (Box 2)
    - Personnel 1988 (Box 2)
    - Participants Bac 1988 (Box 2)
    - Evaluations Bac 1988 (Box 2)
    - Classes/Schedule Bac 1988 (Box 2)
    - Housing BAC 1988 (Box 2)
    - BAC Packet Materials (Box 2)
    - BAC Adult Program 1988 (Box 2)
    - Originals BAC 1988 (Box 2)
    - Personnel 1988 (Box 2)
    - Associate Director 1988 (Box 2)
    - Registrars Applications 1988 (Box 2)
    - Piano Institute 1988 (Box 2)
    - Art Courses 1988 (Box 2)
    - Personnel 1987 (Box 2)
    - Personnel1985 (Box 2)
    - Personnel 1984 (Box 2)
    - Personnel 1983 (Box 2)
    - Personnel 1982 (Box 2)
    - Personnel 1981 (Box 2)
    - Personnel 1980 (Box 2)
    - Summer Facilities Planning Committee1989 (Box 2)
    - Scholarships 1988 (Box 2)
    - Summer Programs Budget 1988 (Box 2)
    - CEU State of CT Info and Forms 1987 (Box 2)
  - 1989-1990
    - Report of the Engineering Education Committee 1989 (Box 3)
    - Summer Programs Administrative Files 1989-1990 (Box 3)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Teaching in Yale College 1989 (Box 3)
    - Summer Facilities Planning Committee Set-Up and Defining Issues 1989 (Box 3)
    - Job Applications 1989 (Box 3)
    - Personnel 1989 (Box 3)
    - Yale Summer Programs Administrative Files 1989-91 (Box 3)
    - Cancelled Courses 1989 (Box 3)
    - Communications 1989 (Box 3)
    - Courses 1989 (Box 3)
    - Housing Applications 1989 (Box 3)
    - Faculty Correspondence 1989 (Box 3)
    - MIS 1989 (Box 3)
    - Provost Office 1989 (Box 3)
    - Planning Group/Old Campus Planning Group 1989 (Box 3)
    - Summer Programs Financial Data 1989 (Box 3)
    - Budget and Recommendations for Administrative Changes 1989 (Box 3)
    - German Students Scholarships 1989 (Box 3)
    - Drama 1989 (Box 3)
    - Summer Program Tallies 1989 (Box 3)
    - International Studies 1990 (Box 3)
    - An Academic Strategy Arts and Sciences 1990 (Box 3)
    - Personnel 1990 (Box 3)
    - Activities: Film, Gym, Etc. 1990 (Box 3)
    - Summer Advisory Committee 1990 (Box 3)
    - Faculty/Program Directors Info. For Annual Report (Box 3)
    - Statistics for Annual Report1990 (Box 3)
    - Art and drama 1990 (Box 3)
    - Bottom Line - Info 1990 (Box 3)
    - Memos to FAS Steering Comm. And Provost Turner (Sept. '90) (Box 3)
    - Faculty Salaries: Problems; Meeting of 31, July 1990 (Box 3)
    - Accounting: Dining Hall, BRT'S 1990 (Box 3)
    - Integrated Calendar 1990 (Box 3)
    - Agreements with Masters 1990 (Box 3)
    - Campus Mail, Air Conditioning, Telephones 1990 (Box 3)
    - Computer 1990 (Box 3)
    - Conference Planning Office, Organization, Mission, Forms 1990 (Box 3)
    - Conferences: Issues 1990 (Box 3)
    - New Haven Hotel Tour 1990 (Box 3)
    - Conference Office: Merger 1990 (Box 3)
    - Course of Study Committee 1990 (Box 3)
    - Elderhostel, Mature Learners 1990 (Box 3)
    - Broad Street 1990 (Box 3)
    - Budget 1990 (Box 3)
    - Summer Facilities Issues 1990 (Box 3)
    - Summer Facilities Planning Committee 1990 (Box 3)
    - Summer Facilities Planning Comm. Set-up and Defining Issues 1990 (Box 3)
    - Policies for Summer Activities Yale: Final Version, Oct. 1. 1990 (Box 3)
    - Summer Loans Statistics 1990 (Box 3)
    - Financial Aid Information 1990 (Box 3)
    - Faculty Information 1990 (Box 3)
    - Foreign Student Info. 1990 (Box 3)
    - HOI 1990 (Box 3)
    - HOI Luncheon: Info. (and some historical info) 1990 (Box 3)
    - Lectures 1990 (Box 3)
    - Letters-Nice 1990 (Box 3)
    - Move from 53 Wall to SSS 1990 (Box 3)
    - NEH 1990 (Box 3)
    - Party - End of Summer 1990 (Box 3)
    - Summer Piano Institute 1990 (Box 3)
    - Problems and Future Change 1990 (Box 3)
    - Publicity 1990 (Box 3)
    - Scholarships 1990 (Box 3)
    - Science Interns 1990 (Box 3)
    - Seminars - One Day 199*0 (Box 3)
    - SLI Faculty Info. 1990 (Box 3)
    - Staffing: People Who Wish to Teach 1990 (Box 3)
    - Tallies 1990 (Box 3)
    - Tuition, General Info. 1990 (Box 3)
    - Tuition, Independent Research in Sciences 1990 (Box 3)
    - Faculty Salaries 1990 (Box 3)
  - 1991
    - Summer Programs Administrative Files 1991 (Box 4)
    - Personnel 1991 (Box 4)
    - Advertising 1991 (Box 4)
    - Humanities and Social Sciences 1991 (Box 4)
    - Summer Sciences 991 (Box 4)
    - Summer Language Institute 1991 (Box 4)
    - ELOP Disbursements 1991 (Box 4)
    - ELOP Other 1991 (Box 4)
    - ELOP Payroll 1991 (Box 4)
    - C.E.U.s 1991 (Box 4)
    - Originals 1991 (Box 4)
    - Policy Statements 1991 (Box 4)
    - Budget 1991 (Box 4)
    - Disbursements 1991 (Box 4)
    - Expense Reports/Student Returns 1991 (Box 4)
    - 91-92 Directory Info (Box 4)
    - Postage 1991 (Box 4)
    - Printing 1991 (Box 4)
    - Purchase Requisitions 1991 (Box 4)
    - Quick Copy 1991 (Box 4)
    - Service Requests 1991 (Box 4)
    - Stock Requisitions 1991 (Box 4)
    - Transfers 1991 (Box 4)
    - C and IS Monthly statements 1991 (Box 4)
    - Conference/Summer Housing Office 1991 (Box 4)
    - Art and drama 1991 (Box 4)
    - Faculty 1991 (Box 4)
    - Storage Space - Council of Masters 1991 (Box 4)
    - Tuition benefits - Policy 1991 (Box 4)
    - Tuition and Salaries 1991 (Box 4)
    - Security 1991 (Box 4)
    - One-Day Seminars 1991 (Box 4)
    - Visiting Faculty 1991 (Box 4)
    - SLI Proposed Budgets 1991 (Box 4)
    - SOM Facility Use 1991 (Box 4)
    - Course Tallies 1991 (Box 4)
    - Budget 1991 (Box 4)
    - Colleges: Masters, Inventories, Locks, Repairs, Money 1991 (Box 4)
    - Colleges: Rotation Schedule 1991 (Box 4)
    - Colleges: Residential Counselors 1991 (Box 4)
    - Colleges: Floor plans, beds 1991 (Box 4)
    - Summer Facilities Planning Committee 1990-91 (Box 4)
    - Conferences 1991 (Box 4)
    - ConferenceServices: VICA 1991 (Box 4)
    - Scholarships 1991 (Box 4)
    - Activities: Film, Gym, Etc. 1991 (Box 4)
    - Advisory Committee 1991 (Box 4)
    - Art and Drama 1991 (Box 4)
    - Broadsheet 1991 (Box 4)
    - Catalogue 1991 (Box 4)
    - CEU 1991 (Box 4)
    - Budget Cutting 1991 (Box 4)
    - Budget Cuts and Reports 1991 (Box 4)
    - Summer Chorus 1991 (Box 4)
    - Classroom Assignments 1991 (Box 4)
    - Course of Study Committee 1991 (Box 4)
    - Custodial Problems, etc. 1991 (Box 4)
    - Registrar 1991 (Box 4)
    - Publicity 1991 (Box 4)
    - Problems and Future Changes 1991 (Box 4)
    - Piano Institute 1991 (Box 4)
    - NEH 1991 (Box 4)
    - Master and Asst. Masters, Summer 1991 (Box 4)
    - Lectures, Readings 1991 (Box 4)
    - Language Lab 1991 (Box 4)
    - HOI Materials 1991 (Box 4)
    - Foreign Student Office 1991 (Box 4)
    - Elderhostel 1991 (Box 4)
    - ELOP 1991 (Box 4)
  - 1992
    - ELOP Disbursements 1992 (Box 5)
    - Purchase Requisitions 1992 (Box 5)
    - Quick Copy (Duplicating) 1992 (Box 5)
    - Service Requisitions 1992 (Box 5)
    - Stock 1992 (Box 5)
    - Accounting Transfers 1992 (Box 5)
    - ELOP Other 1992 (Box 5)
    - CEUS 1992 (Box 5)
    - ELOP Payroll 1992 (Box 5)
    - Piano Institute 1992 (Box 5)
    - Shafer Scholarships 1992 (Box 5)
    - Reserve 1992 (Box 5)
    - CandIS 1992 (Box 5)
    - Art and Drama 1992 (Box 5)
    - Hum. and S.S. 1992 (Box 5)
    - Sciences 1992 (Box 5)
    - SLI 1992 (Box 5)
    - The Broadsheet 1992 (Box 5)
    - Communications 1992 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence/Chrono 1992 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence/Incoming 1992 (Box 5)
    - Payroll (Faculty) 1992 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Appointment Letters 1992 (Box 5)
    - Summer Directory 1992 (Box 5)
    - Summer Handbook 1992 (Box 5)
    - Handbook Update 1992 (Box 5)
    - Handbook Cover 1992 (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous 1992 (Box 5)
    - Elderhostel 1992 (Box 5)
    - Summer Chorus 1992 (Box 5)
    - Course Cancellations 1992 (Box 5)
    - Course Tally 1992 (Box 5)
    - University Information 1992 (Box 5)
    - Personnel 1992 (Box 5)
    - Income/Expense Final Statistics 1992 (Box 5)
    - Summer Housing/Conferences Income/Expense Final 1992 (Box 5)
    - Transfers (and BRT's) 1992 (Box 5)
    - Summer Language Institute Income Info. 1989-92 (Box 5)
    - Budget 1992 (Box 5)
    - Course of Study: Approval of New Courses 12/91 1992 (Box 5)
    - Course of Study: Approval of New Courses 2/92 1992 (Box 5)
    - Drama: Budget, Faculty, Thank you's 1992 (Box 5)
    - Summer Master and Asst. Masters 1992 (Box 5)
    - The Move 1992 (Box 5)
    - Scholarships 1992 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Roster (Salary and Course) 1992 (Box 5)
    - Faculty: Math and Sciences 1992 (Box 5)
    - MandP Salaries 1992 (Box 5)
    - Office Staff Salaries 1992 (Box 5)
    - New Position Defined 1992 (Box 5)
    - Director of Conference Services Position 1992 (Box 5)
    - Tallies 1992 (Box 5)
    - Science T.F. Salaries 1992 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Salaries 1992 (Box 5)
    - Summary Log Book 1992 (Box 5)
    - Yale College Budget 1992 (Box 5)
  - 1993-1994
    - American Russian Youth Orchestra 1993 (Box 6)
    - Report Student Services System 1993 (Box 6)
    - Governance Report 1993 (Box 6)
    - Budget 1993 (Box 6)
    - Art and Drama 1993 (Box 6)
    - Agreements with Masters 1993 (Box 6)
    - Summer Programs and Conferences Schedule 1993 (Box 6)
    - Course of Study Committee 1993 (Box 6)
    - Religious Studies 1993 (Box 6)
    - English Language Institute 1993 (Box 6)
    - Financial Aid/Scholarships 1993 (Box 6)
    - Staffing: faculty 1993 (Box 6)
    - Syllabi 1993 (Box 6)
    - CandT Salaries 1993 (Box 6)
    - MandP Salaries 1993 (Box 6)
    - Tallies 1993 (Box 6)
    - Faculty salaries 1993 (Box 6)
    - Graduate Student Salaries and Payroll Schedule 1993 (Box 6)
    - Tuition 1993 (Box 6)
    - Visiting Faculty Program 1993 (Box 6)
    - Student Yearbook 1994 (Box 6)
    - Summer Chorus 1994 (Box 6)
    - Bottom Line 1994 (Box 6)
    - Lectures 1994 (Box 6)
    - Letters Inquiry and Reply 1994 (Box 6)
    - Budget 1994 (Box 6)
    - Course of Study Committee 1994 (Box 6)
    - Eli 1994 (Box 6)
    - MS/REP Program 1994 (Box 6)
    - NEH Seminars - Housing Problems 1994 (Box 6)
    - U.S. Grant and Old Campus 1994 (Box 6)
    - Physical Plant 1994 (Box 6)
    - Police and Summer Security Policy 1994 (Box 6)
    - Financial Aid for Yale Students 1994 (Box 6)
    - Graduate Student Scholarships (Box 6)
    - SLI - HOI Information 1994 (Box 6)
    - SLI Final Accounting 1994 (Box 6)
    - SLI Comparative Statistics 1994 (Box 6)
    - ESL Phone Issues 1994 (Box 6)
    - Publicity 1994 (Box 6)
    - Courses for Summer 1994 (Box 6)
    - Faculty Lists and Faculty Pay 1994 (Box 6)
    - English 114 1994 (Box 6)
    - SOM 1994 (Box 6)
    - Staffing: People Who Wish To Teach 1994 (Box 6)
    - Glitches 1994 (Box 6)
    - Yale Student Complaint 1994 (Box 6)
    - Student Information 1994 (Box 6)
    - Tallies 1994 (Box 6)
    - Telecommunications 1994 (Box 6)
    - Tuition and Salaries 1994 (Box 6)
    - Visiting Faculty Program 1994 (Box 6)
    - Registrar Notes and Thank You Cards 1994 (Box 6)
    - Athletic Director Reception 1994 (Box 6)
    - Athletics Research 1993/94 (Box 6)
    - AD Search Other Applicants 1994 (Box 6)
    - Report on the Structure of Harvard College 1994 (Box 6)
    - Faculty Handbook Deerfield Academy 1994 (Box 6)
    - Sciences 1994 (Box 6)
    - CESOF Annual Report
      - 1993-94 (Box 6)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 6)
      - 1994 (Box 6)
- Records of the visiting faculty program, 1994-2001; Accession 2003-A-070
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2037
- Annual reports, 1979; Accession 2003-A-072 (Box 1)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2015
- Administrative records, including Special Olympics, 1995-1997; Accession 2004-A-091
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2033
  - SP 95: Course of Study Committee (Box 1)
  - SP 95: CEU (Box 1)
  - SP 95: Agreements with Masters (Box 1)
  - SP 95: Courses (Box 1)
  - SP 95: Faculty/Course/Salary (Box 1)
  - SP 95: Misc. Correspondence (Box 1)
  - SP 96: Faculty (Box 1)
  - SP 96: Summer Director Search (Box 1)
  - SP 96: Budget (Box 1)
  - SP 96: Tuition and Salaries (Box 1)
  - SP 97: Printings (Box 1)
  - SP 97: Faculty Letters (Box 1)
  - SP 97: Faculty Payroll (Box 1)
  - SP 97: Budget (Box 1)
  - Special Olympics, 1995
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 1)
    - Phones (Box 1)
    - Volunteers (Box 1)
    - Officers and Guests (Box 1)
    - Secretary's Office Ad Hoc Committee (Box 1)
    - Receptions Committee Members and Plans (Box 1)
    - Special Events Committee
      - 1994 Apr
      - 1994 May (Box 1)
      - 1994 Jul (Box 1)
      - 1994 Jul (Box 1)
    - Traffic, 1995 July 9 (Box 1)
    - Levin Letter to Faculty, Deans, Directors (Box 1)
    - Facilities Issues; Summer Housing (Box 1)
    - Tent Problem (Box 1)
    - Shuttle Bus Tally, 1995 June 3 (Box 1)
    - Custodial Services (Box 1)
    - Misc. Corr. (signs, buses, volunteers) (Box 1)
    - Special Exhibition - Lorimer (Box 1)
    - RC Levin's Remarks, Media Reception (Box 1)
    - Venue Tour, 1994 July 9 (Box 1)
    - Panning Conference for World Games, 1994 July (Box 1)
    - Sponsor Summit (Box 1)
    - Memo to Officers: Budget Implications of SO (Box 1)
    - Yale Organizing Com. SOWG/Yale Contract (Box 1)
    - CT Special Olympics Invitationals, 1994 (Box 1)
    - From SOWSGA Headquarters UPDATES (Box 1)
    - Development Meeting Minutes (Box 1)
    - Organizational Structure (Box 1)
    - Inception, Policies, Mission Statement, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Official General Information (Box 1)
    - International Awareness Task Force, 1993 September (Box 1)
- Administrative records of the Shafer Scholarship and the Piano Institute, 1982-1999; Accession 2004-A-118
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2035
  - Creation of the Shafer Scholarship (Box 1)
  - Shafer Correspondence (Box 1)
  - General Shafer Information (Box 1)
  - Shafer Clippings (Box 1)
  - Shafer Scholarship, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Shafer Finance, 1983 (Box 1)
  - 1983 (Box 1)
  - 1984 (Box 1)
  - 1985 (Box 1)
  - 1987 (Box 1)
  - 1988 (Box 1)
  - 1989 (Box 1)
  - 1990 (Box 1)
  - 1991 (Box 1)
  - 1992 (Box 1)
  - 1993 (Box 1)
  - 1994 (Box 1)
  - 1995 (Box 1)
  - 1996 (Box 1)
  - 1997 (Box 1)
  - Shafer Labels - Guidance, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Shafer Scholarship, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Piano Institute
    - Forms, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Accept Packet Info, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Inquires, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Accept Packet Info, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Inquires, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Misc., 1991 (Box 1)
- Course evaluations, 1992-2000; Accession 2005-A-108
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - 1992-1996 (Box 1)
  - 1996-2000 (Box 2)
- English Language Institute curriculum records and grade sheets, 1983-2003; Accession 2006-A-148
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2039
  - ITA Course Evaluations, Fall 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ITA Course, Fall 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ITA Evaluations, Fall 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Course Information, Spring 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ELI, Spring 1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ITA Course-Prof Presentation-Advanced Writing, Fall 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Integrated Skills, Group I and Group II, Fall 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Applications-Pronunciation, Spring 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Applications-Presentation Skills, Writing Workshops, Spring 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Applications-Integrated Skills, Spring 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Evaluations and Grades, Fall 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Integrated Skills-Non Grad, Fall 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Spring 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Applications and Grade Reports, Spring 2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Evaluation Forms, Spring 2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Pronunciation-Intro and Advanced, Spring 2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Integrated Skills-Grad, Group I and Group II, Spring 2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Integrated Skills-Non grad, Group III and Group IV, Spring 2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Prof Presentation Skills, Advanced Writing Workshop, Spring 2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Spring Term 2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - ELOP class lists, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Summer Information-ELOP, Summer 1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Summer 1984 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Summer 1986 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Summer 1988 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Summer 1989 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Summer 1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Schedules, Summer 1995 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 5-wk Schedules, Summer 1995 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Schedules, Summer 1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Schedules, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Schedules, Summer 1998 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - 6-wk registration and testing, Summer 1998 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Summer 1999 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Grade Sheet, Summer 1999 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Class Lists, Corrected, Summer 2000 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Summer 2000 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Summer 2001 (Box 2, Folder 38 - 39)
  - Registration and Testing, Opening Week Info, Summer 2001 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Elective Grades, Instructor Comments on Student Work, Summer 2002 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Schedules and Plans, Summer 2003 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Administrative records of the Yale Summer Sessions program, 1950-2005; Accession 2007-A-048
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2041
  - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1962 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1960 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 1959 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 1958 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 1957 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 1956 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 1950-1958 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Summer Directory (2), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Student Directory, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - SLI Project, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Academic Report, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Summer Academic Program and Conf., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Memos, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - SAPandC (2), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Records, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Forms and Handouts, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - SAPandC, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Summer Programs, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Summer Summary (2), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Summer Summary (2), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Student Information, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Annual Summer Report, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - SLI Project, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Course Descriptions, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Yale College Students, 1984-1988 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Courses by year, 1977-1988 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Course of Study Committee, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Course of Study, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Catalog, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Catalog Info, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Information, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Information, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - ExComm, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Courses, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Catalog, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Courses, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Course Proposals, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Courses, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Catalog, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Course of Study Committee, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Annual Report, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Course Proposals, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Catalog, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Course proposal forms, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Course Proposals, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Student records, 2009; Accession 2011-A-042
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2084
  - Summer Program
  - ELI
  - No-Show/Withdrawn
- YSS Student and Study Abroad records, 2002-2010; Accession 2012-A-063
  Boxes 1-13 of this accession contain student records of attendees and records of withdrawn students and no-shows of the 2010 Yale Summer program.
  Restricted until January 1, 2085.
  - Student Records
  - No-Show/Withdrawn Student Records
    - Rejected, 2010
    - No-Show/Withdrawn, 2010
  - Study Abroad Records
    - Receipts & Invoices March '02 – June '02, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 2017)
    - 2005 Annual Report (Box 14, Folder 2018)
    - 2006 Budgets & Salaries (Box 14, Folder 2020)
    - More Accounting – Budgets & Projections, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 2021)
    - 2006 Vendor #'s (Box 14, Folder 2022)
    - 2007 Course Syllabi (Box 14, Folder 2023)
    - Planning, 2006 October - 2007 February (Box 14, Folder 2024)
    - ISA 2007 (Box 14, Folder 2025)
    - RIF Records 2007 (Box 14, Folder 2026)
    - Europe I (Wire Transfers), 2007 (Box 14, Folder 2027)
    - Latin America & Asia (Wire Transfers), 2007 (Box 14, Folder 2030)
    - 2007 Chile Site Visit (Box 14, Folder 2031)
    - 2007 Italy Site Visit (Box 14, Folder 2032)
    - 2007 Site Visit Prague (Box 14, Folder 2033)
    - 2007 Living Allowance – Back up Info (Box 14, Folder 2037)
    - 2007 Living Allowance CRs (Box 14, Folder 2038)
    - HUM-s 250 Rome 2007 Reimbursements (Box 14, Folder 2039)
    - 2007 Russia Reimbursements (Box 14, Folder 2041)
    - Siena (2007 Reimbursements) (Box 14, Folder 2042)
    - 2007 Summer Reimbursements (Box 14, Folder 2043)
    - 2007 Reimbursements Folder I (Box 14, Folder 2044)
    - 2007 Reimbursements Folder II (Box 14, Folder 2045)
    - 2007 Travel Advances (Box 14, Folder 2046)
    - Africa Regional Pilot, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 2048)
    - 2007 YSS Abroad Eval (Box 14, Folder 2049)
    - Group Orientation (Europe), 2007 (Box 14, Folder 2052)
    - 2007 Acceptance Packet Forms (Box 14, Folder 2053)
    - Other Program Evals, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 2054)
    - NUS (2007) (Box 14, Folder 2055)
    - 2007 Non-Yale Student NetIDs (Box 14, Folder 2056)
- Student records, Summer 2011; Accession 2013-A-063
  Restricted until January 1, 2086
  - ELI Attendees
  - ELI No-Shows/Withdrawn
  - ELI Attendees
  - Rejected
  - No Show/Withdrawn